Thank you very much for your support until now.
Hello Project is the best!
Hello! This time I'll be talking with Sakura Ishiyama from JuiceJuice and Momo Kitahara from Ochamidoma.
Yes, I'm Momo Kitahara, and Sakura Ishiyama and I had a chance to meet when we were both trainees at Halo Pro.
She was Kitahara's first junior.
Yes, that's right... and she's so solid and cute... she really has no role to play.
And I'm her first junior... and we had a presentation for the Halo Pro trainees... where we competed against each other in a team competition.
And we were on the same team, Team Tamamushi... the green one, Team Tamamushi... and we had a song we practiced and fought together.
We had a song, and we practiced it together, and then we fought.
We had a song, and we practiced and fought together.
I have good memories of it.
Yes, I was in the team competition.
During the team competition, Kitahara-san did everything steadily and steadily, one by one.
Steady? Steady?
I had the impression that you did everything steadily.
It was my first time in this world of entertainment.
I've learned a lot.
I learned a lot.
I learned a lot from him, and he was a very reliable senior.
I am glad that you are here.
I'm so happy.
So JuiceJuice finished its fall tour about half a month ago.
The fall tour has finished.
At this Nippon Budokan concert, we performed a cover of Mariya Takeuchi's
We performed a cover of Mariya Takeuchi's “Hearty Party Tonight” for the first time
We performed the song for the first time!
The music video has already been uploaded on youtube
You can see a lot of the band members in their normal state in the music video.
I think it's a music video that shows a lot of the members in their everyday lives, so please take a look at it.
The play was called “Mirror Girl”.
It was the first time for us to perform on stage, so I think all the members were very nervous and anxious.
It was a tough rehearsal period since we were going through the 47 prefectures live house tour together.
Yes, there were some difficulties, but we all stuck together and did our best.
Especially at the end of the last MC at the final show, when everyone started crying and saying how much fun we had and how hard we worked, I felt that we had all worked together.
I felt that it was a great experience for me to realize that we all worked hard together.
And now, we are finally going to the final show of the Ochanoma Live Tour 2024 Season 2 in our hometown, Japan.
Our hometown, Japan Jan, will be the last stop on the 47 prefectures live house tour, but the last stop on the fall tour will be in Fukui and Ishikawa prefectures.
The last show of the autumn tour will be held in Fukui and Ishikawa prefectures, and the final show will be held in Natsumi Nakayama's hometown, Ishikawa prefecture.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go!
Grape turtles!
Are you all sparkling? Sparkling!
What do you think? We're all sparkling!
Let's glitter like a mirror ball together today!
Let's be careful, passionate, and careful with each song!
Se-no!
Kamika! Rina! Rin! Kero! Domin! Anna! Bay! Yup! Hanana!
Keep your...
SURPRISE!
Please keep your... SURPRISE!!!
I'm going to do my best!
Oh no.
Today
Wrap
I'm nervous because I'm at a ryokan right now, but I've been working as hard as I can, so I hope I can bring that out properly during this rehearsal period.
Thank you, I promise.
I'll try to do my best, but it tends to happen fast.
I have to admit that I was feeling sad and lonely and lonely and lonely and lonely and lonely and lonely and lonely until yesterday when Kaum graduated.
But now that Kaum is standing up so well, I feel like I'm going to be able to do my best.
I'd like to finish one of them, thinking that I'm already supported by this sparkling power.
Which way after this?
Dan, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Thank you.
I'm going to start you off, but don't waste your time being so gloomy.
Well, here it is, by the way. Sascon.
Well, when this is over, it means I won't be an idol anymore.
I'll do my best to forget all the hard work I've done so far without any regrets.
Also, I really want to spend time with my fans.
I've already done so, but this is the last time I'll be able to sing with the members.
I want to shine brightly on stage and make every moment a memory.
I hope I can make every moment of it a memory.
I'll do my best for Nexo!
I won't cry, I won't cry
Enjoy yourself
Focus, focus
Great, great, great, lots of cameras! Please! Please, please, please!
Which way? Like...
Which one am I?
Either, either, either...
Please! Please!
Thank you!
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, let's engine this thing.
Okay, let's go up the curve.
Let's go up the curve.
Killer. Killer.
Keep going, keep going!
Keepyah, killer!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go!
GALAXY
Yes, a titillatingly perfect hand!
Contact, Atalie.
Batterly, Atalie.
It's your lucky day down there.
You can be me just the way I am
You're a hero for staying.
So, yeah.
Let's love the weird
With pops, steps, and sharp
Sharp as a rake, mooning kiss
Life's a theater
Drink it, shag it, and be done with it
Actors are Gigametal
GALAXY
Shubidobi, shubidobi no GALAXY
Let's eat up the time!
GALAXY
Traffic jam, highway, colorful contact
Ha! Ha!
Shaking dust, love, sweet lodging, enjoy
Aha! General situation, emotion
Yabai, gesu, bus, deta coin
Hakta!
Sneaking, twitching, twitching
Dictionary
Come on!
Like a musical or Flash Bob
Everyday except with you
Champai
Surely, let's wake up a lifetime
Combo Convocation
Absolutely, hopelessly, up to adversity
Let's write numbers, let's write numbers
The timing is perfect.
What an eternity, because eternity is
A collection of moments, moments, moments
Ladies and gentlemen
A gradation that captures the attention of the entire universe
The hottest dramatic romantic comedy in the galaxy
The star of the show is, of course
IT'S YOU
Yes, it's true.
Let's add a little extra strangeness
Snap!
Crackle!
That's right.
I'll spare you the weirdness.
Okay!
Pop, step, jump.
Writing is a must for the mission.
Life is in the 90s, for sure
Life is in the nineties.
Hey.
Ride and shuffle along
Awaagaki ga metal
If it's a seven
I'll light you up for life
Let's change the numbers
Let's rewrite the numbers.
Your timing is exquisite
Oh, my God, what an eternity
A collection of moments.
Galaxy, galaxy, galaxy.
Shu-kiri-shu-kiri-shu-kiri-shu-kiri-shu. Galaxy.
Galaxy. Galaxy. Galaxy.
Water, air, earth, fire, wood, earth, heaven, sea
water, chi, earth, fire, wood, earth, heaven, sea
Defeat is the last battle
Hope you enjoyed it.
Sakura Ishiyama, the juice juice and
Momo Kitahara of Tea Horse bring you Haloste.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
so let's not think too much and answer them quickly and at a good tempo.
I'll do my best.
Less than four weeks to go this year.
What was the most memorable event in 2024?
The stage
On stage.
Working with Ms. Kurimoi Kamiko of Angulum in a magazine that came out last week. What did you feel during the photo shoot?
Professional
Ocha-no-Ma Hello Kitty tour goods are now on sale What do you think is particularly unique about your illustrations?
My lower eyelashes.
What is the key point of your daily makeup?
My eyelashes.
It will be 3 years next week since the name of the Ocha-no-Ma group was announced.
Professional
How has the tea ceremony changed over the past three years, and how have our bonds deepened?
Thank you so much for all the amazing eyelashes!
I wonder what it is... I asked you a question about the key points of my daily makeup... How do you keep your eyelashes from becoming panda eyes?
There's a simple mascara that comes right off with hot water, but we sweat a lot.
And I'm particular about my eyelashes because there's a limit to how far I can raise them with an eyelash curler, so I heat them up with a hair dryer.
So we heat them up with a hair dryer.
So I heat them up with a hair dryer and raise them with heat, like a hot brower I made myself.
I also use different mascaras and colored mascaras.
I'm trying different mascaras, using colored ones, fashionable ones, using ones with licks in them, etc. I'm trying various things.
I was working with Ms. Ryomoe Kamiguni of Angstrom, and I felt something professional during the photo shoot.
I was able to observe her posing in this kind of place, and I could see her expressions and the way she was posing.
The expressions and poses that came out were so cool, and I was so impressed that he winked at me here.
I was so impressed with his posing, and I thought he was very professional.
It's a magazine called “Souen”, and it's a magazine I've wanted to be in for a long time.
I wanted to be in it so much that I went to my manager and asked to be in Souen.
I wanted to be in the magazine so much that I went to my manager to ask to be in Souen.
There were so many things that I really wanted to be in.
I thought it was a glittering and dreamy world.
I burned it into my eyes and thought it might be my last time.
I always enjoy seeing it burned into my eyes.
I've always enjoyed it, but when I do magazine shoots.
I think it's fun to be able to see myself in a way I've never seen before, or to realize that I can be like this.
I would like to continue to challenge myself in the future.
Sakura-chan's question will be asked after the vtr.
I went to school in Japan and
me
me, I really like today's concert...
The title of the concert is “Kirakira”, so...
so we put a lot of sparkling elements in the concert.
and the performance was full of sparkles.
The roots of Angelem
I think it was a wonderful performance that will remain in the history of Angelem.
I hope you had a good time.
Okay, one more.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, Carmina.
I was really sad to see Carmina's last performance.
I felt really sad because it was the last stage for Carmina, but I could enjoy it as much as I could.
I was really happy to see so many people at the venue, on the live streaming, and in the live game.
There might be more live videos than the house, so please check it out!
Please check it out!
So, what did you think of today's star, Ayana Kawamura?
It seems like it's finally here.
This tour is called the Taste Anniversary Tour.
I'm very happy to be able to participate at this time.
The next concert will be filled with lots of sparkles.
It was the most dazzling and sparkling time!
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you so much for spending Kawamura's idol life with Angsty!
Thank you very much.
We will continue to do our best in Angulum, so please support us!
So, that's all for Angulum!
Next, I would like to ask Sakura-chan some questions.
I'll do my best.
Hearty Party music video is being shown tonight!
If JuiceJuice were to have a Christmas party, what would you be in charge of, Sakura-chan?
Tastemaker.
Rosie Chronicle will perform as a back-up dancer at the Nippon Budokan on November 19.
What inspires you about Rosie Chronicle?
Her attitude to keep looking forward.
Now
Sakura-chan's secret effort is not to eat too much. Today's breakfast is boiled curry.
What is the word that you think is perfect for looking back on the year 2024 of Juice Juice?
Thank you very much I was looking forward to the food quite a bit
Okay, I'd like to ask you some questions, but first of all, I, Kitahara, thought of this question, “What's for breakfast today? Curry?
Yes, in Italy it was curry
Did you have fish?
It was brown, like simmered or teriyaki fish.
It was brown? It's so delicious. Did you make that yourself?
I had to go to another job earlier, but I bought this while I was there.
It looks delicious.
I just had it for breakfast and it was delicious.
If we're having a Christmas party here at JuiceJuice, Sakura-chan isn't in charge.
Tasting? She's cute.
I'm pretty sure I'd be in charge of setting up the party.
Even if we were preparing together, I'm sure I'd be snacking on the food.
The kind they don't know about.
So, while we're talking about “tasting,” we're talking about protecting the members, right?
I think it's a perfect word to describe the goodness of the whole body.
how about this one? well... after Ms. O-rimen graduated... what do you call it?
I think it was the year 2024 that all the members of the new Juice Juice team were looking forward to the year ahead.
I think it was a year in which all the members were looking forward to the future, and this time, each member was doing their best in their own way for the Triangle Groove 2 Special.
Haloste will continue after this!
Halostay!
Sakura Ishiyama from Juice Juice and Momo Kitahara from Tea Horse
Momo Kitahara of Ocha-no-Ma presents “Halostaye”.
From here on, we'll be taking you behind the scenes of Hello Project members' rehearsals.
We'll be bringing you “HaloViHa”!
Have you ever seen this “HaloViHa” corner?
Yes, I have!
I saw a video of Kazuka Arisawa of Juice Juice playing the violin in the orchestra.
Ichika is always so cheerful and funny.
She's always so cheerful and funny, but she's so serious about her violin.
It was so cool to see her playing the violin so seriously.
I told her that this is what I wanted to see.
I said, “I want to see this kind of thing.
This is a close-up of her at the time of the orchestra.
I'm sure you wouldn't have been able to see it if it was just a close-up.
That's right.
Icika spent a lot of time alone with the violin that day.
Icika spent a lot of time alone with the violin
She spent a lot of time alone with the violin
That's why it's such a mess.
Thank you very much for watching my favorite video.
I'm so glad that your fans were able to see the behind-the-scenes stuff that you can only see at events like the orchestra.
I'm very happy that fans were able to see the behind-the-scenes stuff that you can only see at events like the orchestra and such.
So this time, I'd like to introduce to you the following members of Morning Musume。
Yumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 24, who was photographed by Non-no Web.
Please take a look.
Move it around a little bit if you're curious.
Thank you very much.
This beige...
My own?
Beige dog-dog.
I really should have taken him to a stuffed animal hospital.
I should have taken him to the stuffed animal hospital.
Is he really cute?
He's adorable!
His face.
His face is adorable.
Maybe I'll have him hold her in his arms or something.
I'd like that.
They're all so cute.
So cute!
I'm going to do a photo shoot and interview for Non-no Web today.
I'll be doing it. I'm so happy that they are planning to do a one-man shoot like this for my graduation.
By the way, this is for your information. I love stuffed animals, and I have several of them at home,
I have several stuffed animals at home, and I said that I would like to take pictures with them.
I asked to have my picture taken with some of the stuffed animals that I brought and some that were prepared for me. I am so happy!
You are doing this all by yourself, aren't you? Do you get nervous because you have done so many?
Yes, I do. I mean, am I sure I can handle the subject?
But I have a lot of people on my side today!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much.
It's delicious. Thank you for taking my picture.
It's so cute.
Oh, wow. - Oh, wow.
I'm smiling.
Cute.
So cute!
I'm looking forward to this.
I'll bring this
Cute!
CAUTIE
Start playing cheapest
It's been a while.
Cute little thing...
I woke up from sleep.
I can make a face like I woke up from sleep!
LOL
It's so cute!
Molly Molly Hiiri
Yeah, the interaction feels good.
I don't know if I'd call that filming.
Ishida is flirting with his father.
Nice video!
Panda
Panko was given to me for the main part.
Pio.
Kamla Ayano said I looked like Mr. Ishida.
She said I look like Mr. Ishida.
Is it that? Because it's his debut?
Yes, she's a chick, and she said I look like I'm dancing.
It's like she's dancing.
She's cute, isn't she?
This girl...
There it is!
There she is!
I don't think this is a good idea.
Excuse me.
It's like you do it like this, like this.
Like this.
Pito.
Excuse me.
Good-bye.
There's a shooting star on my face.
There are shooting stars on my face.
Thank you for watching.
Was there anything you were conscious of?
I was consciously aware of Kangoku Ryumoe.
This time, the hair and make-up artist asked me who I wanted to be. He asked me who I wanted,
I decided to call Non-san, whom I usually follow on Instagram.
Guri Kawashima, who often does Kamiko's...
You do her makeup too.
Yes, that's right.
Today is the day that many of my longings came true!
These sparkles are done with a sense of style.
She did it with flair.
And this...
Do you have a favorite color? He asked me if I had a favorite color.
I said, “Blue” from the members.
and he chose blue.
Music
I'm in, I'm in
I smiled a little
by H.
Ise-san, you've really raised your expressive power.
No, but it's the whole world view.
Makeup, styling, lighting, and so on.
I've been given the opportunity to be a part of it.
I don't think I'm at all
When I was asked to do this kind of shoot
I felt like all these people...
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it with
I think it's better to do it with this kind of hand.
I thought, “How can I get good at this?
I wondered how I could get good at it, so I looked at a lot of things.
I also like to dance, so I think it would be cool if my body was at an angle when I play.
It's an extension of dancing.
I wanted my fans to see me like this.
I wonder if I do this kind of research because I want my fans to look at me this way.
I'm sorry. I have to do it right.
I have to be good at what I do.
For example, I respect the choreographer when he gives me a part to dance, and I respect him when he gives me this part to sing.
I have to respect the choreographer when I'm given a part to dance, or when I'm given a part to sing, for example.
And since I'm asked to do the filming, too.
I'm the one who's going to show it to the world.
I have to do it.
I don't know if I can do it yet.
I still don't know how to make clothes look beautiful.
I've met a lot of people, so I've come to that conclusion.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry for being so busy before graduation, but as far as I can tell.
I thought you must be busy.
Busy?
But I think you have to be busy.
So I'm just saying thank you for everything.
Because if I'm not busy now.
I'd have graduation fever.
If I didn't have that fever, there would be no point in graduating.
Thank you for everything.
I think there are experiences that I wouldn't have had if I hadn't announced my graduation.
Like the fact that I was able to have a photo shoot by myself.
I think that Ishida's name will be mentioned because of the graduation.
I'm really enjoying it now.
What do you have in mind?
I think there are a lot of things at that timing, but I felt it at that time.
Brave dance, album song, the latest song on the album.
That's also the reason why Tsunku was my
I felt like Tsunku might have been inspired by my feelings when I asked him about my graduation. I had the feeling that Tsunku was inspired by my feelings when I asked him about my graduation,
I know that kind of thing because I am the one who announced the graduation.
It's a nuance.
Morning Musume。 I had a lot of fun with Morning Musume。
I'm saying that I had a lot of fun during my time with Morning Musume。
But there are some things
feelings that I didn't like in myself
or feelings of jealousy
I can't wait
I want to graduate and go it alone.
I want to graduate and do it on my own.
Tsunku is expressing that feeling in a very big way.
I don't know...
I don't have it.
Like, "I don't want to just wait.
I was thinking, "Now's the time.
I've heard that a lot.
Fresh... you don't have to ask this much, do you?
Do you ever want to do this? Yuma Ishida of Warning Musume。 Yuma Ishida of Waring Musume。
She's graduating because she doesn't want to do this anymore.
To be honest, I've done everything I want to do.
There are things I want to do, and there are things I wish I could have done, but...
Have I done all I want to do?
You still have to do it.
Good luck with Marukura.
Thank you very much.
VTR.
Yes, I watched the VTR.
I really admire your coolness, Mr. Ishida.
I really thought that the video was filled with all the things I respect about Mr. Ishida and his coolness.
And seeing Mr. Ishida surrounded by stuffed animals
It's as if the stuffed animals are really alive!
It's amazing.
I felt that the presence of Mr. Ishida made the stuffed animals seem more alive, and I felt that this is the power that he has.
How did you like it, Sakura-chan?
I thought it was a very fun shoot with your various faces, costumes and makeup.
I also thought that it must have made her fans very happy to see her feelings toward her graduation.
So, please look forward to the next episode of HaloviFa!
November 28, 2024
My life as an idol, filled with dreams
My life as an idol, filled with dreams, is about to come to an end.
When I was a little girl, I dreamed of becoming an idol
15 years later, I have been supported and loved by so many people
I have so many people cheering me on and loving me
I can feel that the world is so sparkling and shining
I can feel that the world is full of love.
My first stage was in a fish market of a supermarket, a park and a parking lot.
There was no one to see me, and I often sang to the sky in the distance.
But what I experienced there was very important.
It has strengthened the roots of Ayano Kawamura.
I have been desperately searching for what I can do
I challenged myself and kept going.
Rather than giving up, I wanted to stick with it, so I auditioned and became a member of Hello Project.
I became a member of Hello Project
I was welcomed by kind seniors and joined Angelem.
From Ai-chan to Kabam
I was also able to join the group with Funa-chan, who is very reliable and lovely, as my classmate.
It was very encouraging.
After two years, she became a sub-leader of the group.
Congratulations!
I've been thinking a lot about what I can do for Angeleum, and I've been challenging myself.
Sometimes I switched the microphone to a knife and did a tuna dismantling show.
I'm happy that my various activities have been enjoyed by our fans.
The members of Angelem keep on graduating and joining the group, but the passion of Angelem
But the passion of Angelem will always remain the same.
I've been so happy to be in an environment and situation where I can work hard.
Being able to perform at venues like the Budokan and Yokohama Arena every year.
Thanks to the members and the fans who support us
I was able to make many of my dreams come true
I was able to see many dreams come true.
I was taught a lot of love through my activities in Angstrom.
To love myself, to love my friends, to love the people around me
and the great love from my fans.
Because I am a muddy and full of human nature
I'm so busy living as Ayano Kawamura that tears flow down my face
There were many times when I wanted to run away from such a weak me
Thank you for watching.
But the days when you, the fans, wrapped me with your great love were very warm.
All the tears I shed in Angeleum were tears with meaning.
I shed many tears and that's why I became a member of Angelem.
I believe that everything is connected and there is no such thing as a wasted experience.
My life as an idol, I kept swimming as fast as I could.
The tears I shed in Angulum
They are unique, colorful, and sparkling.
It was so interesting and I'm glad that I worked so hard.
I've received so much love.
I feel so invincible.
When I moved to Tokyo
I wanted to repay everyone's kindness
I thought I wanted to be rich
The love I received from everyone
The days we laughed together
and the tears I shed.
Congratulations!
All those sparkling things, all those precious things that no amount of money could ever acquire.
I have packed them all in my treasure box, tied them with a ribbon, and will treasure them forever.
To my fans, among so many idols in the world, thank you for finding me, supporting me, and loving me,
Thank you so much for your support and love.
In your daily lives from now on,
I hope that in your daily life, you will find something sparkling, such as bonito or tuna,
I hope you will remember Ayano Kawamura in your daily life.
You illuminated me with your light purple penlights and made me shine,
Thank you so much for making me a sparkling stew idol.
I hope that Ayano Kawamura will continue to be a first-class star shining in your hearts.
Thank you for the too many happy days. Ayano Kawamura.
Those were good times.
If your life is stuck in the memories of the past
It's really boring.
Without even seeing it with your own eyes
Just by the voices of those around me
I don't want to be stuck in these long years
I don't want to get stuck in it.
It's a quick death, and you have to look back on it
We've got to change the times
Let's change the times
I want to stay here forever and ever more
I wish I could dream more.
But I've got to go.
It's time to go
♪ This is where it all starts
Give me a big push, give me a big push
It's a long time ago now
The short skirts you've been wearing since before you knew it
And the short cut that I cut off
It's all in the past now
I'm not 15 years old anymore, and I'm not just dreaming
You can't move forward with just a smile on your face 24 hours a day
I read in books about love and romance.
I'm not sacrificing anything
You're right. I'm kind of...
I'm about to cry, but I'm gonna take on all my expectations
I'm going to move forward without looking back.
Even if I want to be a little spoiled
I'll be different tomorrow
Before I know it, I'll be an adult
I can't be honest, I'm too naive
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you for these words.
From the bottom of my heart. From the bottom of my heart.
Always, always, here.
Always here.
I wish I could dream more, but I have to go.
But I have to go now.
It's time to go. I'm gonna untie your hands.
This is where it all starts
Give me a big push
Look at me
Let's do it again tomorrow.
Let's do our best tomorrow
Sakura Ishiyama of Juice Juice and
and Momo Kitahara from Tea Horse
It's time to say goodbye!
How did you like the two of us MCing together, Sakura-chan?
Yes, it was the first time for me and Kitahara-san to work together as MCs.
It was the first time for me and Kitahara-san to work together as MCs.
It was a very fresh feeling.
I also felt that it was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time since I've worked alone with Kitahara-san.
I was so happy to work alone with her, and I was able to see JuiceJuice's performance at the Budokan, and I saw how mature Sakura-chan has become.
Sakura-chan had grown up so much, I felt like her mother in a mysterious way.
She was so beautiful or sparkling and her performance ability had improved so much that I was really happy as one of the senior trainees.
I'm so happy to be able to tell that to her.
I'd like to announce that Ochanoma Live Tour 2024 Season 2, Our hometown is Japan!
The autumn tour was very long, but now it's coming to the end, I'm a little sad, but at the same time, I'm very happy.
We are a little bit sad, but we hope we can give you a great show that is suitable for the last show.
Juice Juice will be performing at the Chikappa Festival 2024 on December 8!
We are very happy to be able to perform at the Chikappa Festival again this year. We will do our best.
And from January 2 next year, I will perform at the Hello! Project 2025 Winter Fest Write to GO!
I think it's cool that the title is written in one kanji character,
The set list of "Shokubuku" is designed to make each group shine,
GO!" is a setlist that transcends the boundaries of the groups.
GO! is a mix and match of the two groups, which we are really looking forward to.
We are really looking forward to it!
Haloste is a channel where the members of Hello Project
GO! is a channel where the members of Hello Project appear more and more often!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel!
Our partners are Sakura Ishiyama of Juice Juice and Momo Kitahara of Ocha no Oma.
and Momo Kitahara of Ocha no Mama!
Farewell!
This is really the last song!
I will always, always love you all!
Love, love, love
Seino
I swear I'll protect you for the rest of my life
How many times in your life
If I love you, I can say it.
I'm a little embarrassed
I'm so busy that I'm dizzy
I'm so busy I can't even see my own eyes.
Dear customers, how many people have I passed in front of the station?
Listen, this is the age of cheap love
Women and men are all free
History
Before leaving the move
Hot hands must touch
No, no, no, no, love
Let's go for a ride
With Lovelace after all
Earth goes round and round till the universe
Let's ride on the sky
With big Lovelace
4.6 billion years beyond love
Love Love
LOVE LOVE LOVE
Love Love Love
Love Love
Seino
OH OH OH OH
If you could survive...
Where's the reason to stay alive?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm so lost and I'm so lost and I'm so lost and I'm so lost and I'm so lost
I'm afraid to go to bed early
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
everyone can resist for an hour
I don't know if you know what I'm talking about, of course you're crying
If you get hurt, if you get hurt
If I could tell you, it would just go on and on
The age of you and me
It's the only way, it's the only way, it's the only way, it's the only way
I don't have to be the person I lived my dream to be
I'll really live
I'm living the feeling right now
Let's just ride it out, after all, it's love, right?
♪ Round the earth, round the earth, round the universe
Let's ride it out. It's a big love, isn't it?
Love will transcend 4.6 billion years
If there's no conflict in the future
What's the point if someone else has to endure
I'm trying to make a dream
Even if it's not me
I'll really live
The way I'm feeling right now
Let's just ride it out. After all, it's love, isn't it?
♪ Round the earth, round the universe
Let's ride it out. It's a big love, isn't it?
Love transcends 4.6 billion years
Love, love, love
More!
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Thank you very much!
It was Azumi!
Thanks Aya!
This way!
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much!
LOL!
It was sparkling.
Thank you.
I thought...
I thought so.
It was great.
Laughs.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
LOL.
LOL!
I got it.
Please take good care of it.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
LOL!
I love you.
I love Ayano.
I'm not done with this one yet.
Christmas party!
LOL!
And the all-important tan play.
Yeah, that's right...
And the time camera in ten years.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
I knew it.
Where is it?
It's at my house.
You'll have to remember.
Of course!
I, Ayano Kawamura, graduated from Angstrom and Hello Project on November 28, 2024.
I had a very happy idol life with the support of so many people.
I have many memories of Haloste, but recently I was very happy to be able to make a boat in Thailand and to be able to perform at Hello Kitchin for the last time.
It was the best start of my career.
It was a great start.
I want to thank you for your support of Anchoroom.
And for supporting Aino Kawamura, thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
Project fans.
Project fans are watching our show.
Project's concerts and so on.
Project concerts.
But, um, thank you so much for putting that in my eyes.
Project concert or something like that...
Thank you for watching me.
I was very happy to be a part of Halo Project.
Halo Pro is the best!
This is Ayano Kawamura.